Hello friends, I am Ankur Upadhyay,
welcome to your own
YouTube channel Share Market Analysis.
Friends, here I will talk to you all about
a stock in
which a block deal is going to happen tomorrow, that
too for a big amount and at a good discount. Will the
stock fall or rise? The
name of the stock is Amar Raja Batteries. There is a
deal of about 14% in the share, so I
will share that with you all right now. Ashok Leyland is at a 52-week high
in the stock and the
entire auto sector is in a good boom. The opinion
of this stock is big now. The company will get a big order worth Rs 800 crore. We will
understand its details.
Wipro was in a stormy boom after its results.
In today's session, others are also suggesting
that this is just the beginning and there will be a boom.
Policy IndusInd Bank, ICC Lombard and
ITTA are to release their quarterly numbers tomorrow, so
these stocks are going to be on your radar anyway.
And before all this, I would like to
share with you all what are the US market and
global markets indicating for tomorrow. So let's
start by first understanding
that market.  In terms of how
the market is looking, two zones are almost
flat, you can be positive,
give me 0.20%, a gain of 70 points is being
seen in the downtrends,
next is up by more than half a percent,
give me 0.60%, it is
seen trading above 84, the Nifty 500 is seen 1/4% flat,
but if you give a hundred percent in 2000, then
it is looking good, if we
talk about the global market, first of all let's look at Asia
Pacific, it is flat
in the red, Shanghai is seen down by about 1%,
Hang Seng is not showing anything, the market is just a
story, I think
maybe nothing is visible at all,
here let's talk about the European market, the
Nifty is trading at about 0.4%, the Nifty is trading at
0.23%, the Nifty is rising by 1%, so
how can you see the market is outperforming, nothing
else is happening,
if we talk about
Nifty, then here you still have to
see the boom  It is getting a gain of about 33
points and
you are seeing a gift gift at the levels of 7, 1971.
Now coming to India, I
want to talk about the rate of Wipro.
First of all, there will be a storm in Wipro stock
and the level of 412 that
they have determined is really a big breakout.
I would consider that the one who has a direct
target of up to 440. According to me,
whoever has it should hold, but today
in the second half, some profit booking has been seen in IT on a
technical basis or collection. The
IT index has banded 600 points below that. So,
how is the trade response tomorrow, that will be
more important, but right now
Wipro is showing 2.5% up.
Infosys area is showing 0.8% up, so it is looking
very good, it is looking good,
but there is no bullishness here, there is bullishness,
look at the area of
HDFC Bank, if you look at the area of
HDFC Bank, after the results of HDFC Bank came today, there was a
2% up gesture, but India is moving 4%  I have been telling
you from the beginning that
this stock is not for trading, now
this stock is for investment, it has
not done anything in the last one year, the profit is constant at 25%,
if it is increasing then the price of the stock will
increase brother, it will increase someday, it is a blue chip company, it is the
second largest company of India, its
name is in the top ten banks of the world,
why won't the stock move, it will definitely move, if there is
fear then don't sell,
before 2000, keep a clear cut in your hand, hold it as if
you have made HD of your money, nothing more than this, let's
talk about the next stock,
here it is written that Ashok Leyland is
getting orders worth about 800 crores, so
this is a big news, it is visible
for this top, on the basis of which the stock has
shown good moves today, highs have been placed
almost at its 52 week high, now
how can I trade this stock further, let's
try to understand its high,
see today the stock has
closed at the level of 172.40,
today a high of 174.70 has been placed on this stock, which is its
52  The same is being seen this week, the stock has
seen a rise after a long time,
I will tell you that on 21st July, the quarterly earnings
of the stock are also going to come, so that will be a matter to watch, the
company has touched the market cap of ₹50000 crore, I will
share it with you from the technical view because it is
interesting, it should be done with the sale of 168, let's move
ahead for the targets of 175, 1880, next stock Amar Raja
Batteries, as I told in the beginning
that you have to keep this stock on your radar tomorrow,
listen to the complete details, only after that
take any decision,
now sorry Clarius A R B L
Holding LG, you will probably sell its entire
estate which is 14%, they have the entire
beach, in this way, I am also a
lion devotee, instead of falling,
I will share that too with you, why it happens,
almost in tomorrow's session, blog deal,
like in Amar Raja Batteries tomorrow, where they are going to
sell their entire estate, Clarius A
R B L Holding is 14% stock
What has their floor price done to them,
currently the stock was traded at 685 at a price of 651, which
means you can say that it has gone down by Rs 34, which
means there is a discount of almost more than 5%, but
because they are trading in the middle, you
can take a positive from the market that they might have oversold,
you are tension free, a lion
can run away, so whether it falls or rises is a
matter to be seen, I will not comment on this,
but yes I will definitely say that tomorrow this
stock should definitely be on your radar,
now here are some such stocks which are going to give
you quarterly number page tomorrow, if we
talk about big names then Pali Cap which is
continuously going strong, is an excellent company,
if you go to normal retail shops
also, where you will see what is happening
in the virus, then they will tell you only six, there are
two reasons behind Pali, one is that the
shopkeeper's margin is getting made and
secondly, the stock is
strong, so it is running at a different
level, now
how will you see the results of late, I hope that  They
should come out well but there has already been a lot of division,
you should know about that too.
IndusInd Bank should know the numbers in the open market. It remains to be
seen how they come today.
HDFC Bank should post good numbers.
ICC Lombard Insurance will
post its numbers tomorrow. It remains to be seen
how they come. After that, it will be on the platform for SBI Life and
HDFC Live,
brother, how will the numbers come in future.
LT
LC from these banks have come today. Your LT has come,
so numbers have already come from Meet's UP. It remains to be
seen
how LDS presents its numbers tomorrow. So, you must have
liked both the videos completely.
Thank you, so have a great day watching this video on match.